Marlene Park and Gerald E. Markowitz research materials on New Deal art
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Sound Recordings, 1974-1976, Series 4:; (Boxes 5-6; 0.3 linear ft.)
  Sound recordings (5 sound reels and 16 audiocassettes) contain interviews and class discussions with various artists conducted by Park and Markowitz at the John Jay College of Criminal Justice.
  Recordings are organized by format. Within each format, they are arranged alphabetically by artist.
  Artists' files (series 2) also include sound recordings.
  - Barnet - Solman, 1975, undated, (4 sound tape reels) (Box 5)
  - Wolins, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 5)
  - Alston, undated, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Barnet, 1974, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Bolotowsky, 1976, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Cillaluetue, 1975, (2 folders; 2 sound cassettes) (Box 6)
  - Citron, Minna, 1974, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Chreiren, S., undated, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Cronbach, 1975, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Leskinsky, A., undated, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Loew, 1975, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Muralists Panel, 1975, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Reisman, Philip, 1975, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Rothschild, L., 1974, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Solman, 1974, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Toney, A., undated, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)
  - Wolins - Artists, 1974, (1 sound cassette) (Box 6)